What would you take to be the best?
Take Your Pills is a documentary film directed by Alison Klayman.
In a hypercompetitive world, drugs like Adderall offer students, athletes,
coders and others a way to do more -- faster and better.
But at what cost?
Self - Former NFL Player (as Eben), played by Eben Britton.
Self - Political Theorist, UC Berkeley, played by Dr. Wendy Brown.
Self - College Sophomore, played by Ariana.
Self - College Junior, played by Delaney.
Self - College Senior (as Jasper), played by Jasper Holt-Teza.
Self - College Senior, played by Leigh.
Take Your Pills is an hour-long American documentary from 2018, directed by
Alison Klayman and produced by Motto Pictures and Netflix Studios.
The documentary explores the positives and negatives of taking
psychostimulant medications such as Adderall.
The film is a series of interviews with college students and working adults who are prescribed stimulants for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD),
along with parents who touch on the difficulties of raising children with ADHD and interviews with professionals commenting on the use of stimulants.
Those interviewed include former player for the NFL's Jacksonville
Jaguars Eben Britton, and neuroscientist Anjan Chatterjee.
The film's executive producers were Maria Shriver and Christina
Schwarzenegger; its world premiere was at the SXSW film festival in 2018.